LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now.
Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may shallow you, flying in glory
It is a time when the internet spans the world
and even though consciousness
has been transformed into light and electrons
all flowing in a single direction
discrete individuals have not yet
coalesced into a single consciousness
The device to inject sleeping gas into the air conditioning
system is now installed between the outer wall and the roof.
Roger... Set it to 0-2-2-0,
and wait for the sign....
Are you guys cops!?
The system is no longer capable of justice...
If you don't like this world,
change yourself first!
If you don't like that idea, close your
eyes and ears, keep your mouth shut, and live in solitude!
If you don't like that either...
Major...
Call everyone, tell them to equip with A-2...
The location is 82-D3...
You hear that, Batou?
Yeah, I'm listening...
Public Safety
Section 9
I can't hand over command without a good reason!
This case is under Police jurisdiction!
I have no responsibility to explain it to you...
Don't be stubborn, just hand
over command to the military...
Same to you!
Is this time to be selfishly quarreling?
Aramaki!
The real problem is the customers inside, right?
The customers who believe to be captured
are: the Minister of Foreign Affairs,
The minister's secretary, the chairman of
the minister's supporters organisation and
two visitors from the North American
Industry Support Association...
It's been 17 minutes since the
geisha robots captured them.
The hostess, who escaped on her own, said
that two of them might have been killed.
Other than that, we don't have a clue of
the situation inside the restaurant...
Any claim of responsibility or demands?
Not at this point...
Communication blockade?
We're on...
Media blackout?
It's been 9 minutes since we executed
Code 1-4, it won't last long...
We, Public Safety Section 9, will
be taking over this case now.
Standby until then.
Kubota...
Tell me why the army wants to be involved...
One of our men is inside.
I can't tell you more than that for now.
Alright, tell me about it later.
Leave it to me.
Major!
Not yet!
The army wants to be involved...
Watch your back!
Thanks for the advice...
Batou!
Not yet!
So that was the wiretap I heard when I was listening
in on the Sniping Group's communications...
Togusa! Ishikawa!
Major, there are too many lines.
It'll take me at least 2 hours to find it.
Togusa! Go out to the courtyard,
and be ready to strike!
Roger!
Saitou!
Although I neutralised the image curtain,
There are too many trees, so I
can only do limited sniping...
Pazu! Bouma!
Anytime
The guy who's controlling the
robot geishas must be close,
Don't shoot the transmitter though.
Send the virus out before the
guy erases the evidence!
Major! What if the robot
geishas demand better working conditions?
You...
Everyone stay put!
Stand-by OK!
Good, strike!
Go!
Pazu! Bouma!
Follow the hunting virus!
Batou support them!
Sounds great!
Don't space out Togusa!
Chief! We have the scene under control.
One of the hostages needs emergency treatment...
There's a severe external wound...
The other one, judging from the damage
to the head, is confirmed dead...
Batou and the others are pursuing the culprit.
Good, guide the minister and the
rest out of the restaurant...
But be alert!
I have the passage lighted and 4
wagons ready at the main entrance...
Move to alert level B-6
Roger.
Minister, can you walk?
Yeah... thanks for helping me...
Major! The target is a cyborg...
Cross-referencing records.
No matches so far.
Don't kill him until we know
what he was waiting for...
Bouma! I'm going to catch up with you soon!
Don't jump out in front of the car!
Do I look like a child?
Tachikoma! Are you following me?
What took you so long, Tachikoma!
Give up yet...?
Shit... I might've screwed up...
Come in.
So, will you tell me the story, now?
Yes, the minister's secretary, the
one shot in the head... was my subordinate.
She was under my command, and I ordered
her to make secret inquiries...
Inquiries about the minister?
Yes, there seems to be some interest around
him lately regarding the Ichinose Report...
The one that contains scenarios for diplomatic
and military tactics in an emergency, right?
Yes, of course the army won't refuse if
the minister wants us to release it...
But it wasn't the minister
himself who ordered it...
And we managed to stall them until now...
The inquiry was what you'd call a
confirmation of safety, just normal business.
Then why was she shot?
Hm? She might have been erased
because she knew something...
How did the Minister's background check out?
I looked into it briefly but nothing...
He wasn't being threatened and there was
no unusual activity in his account either.
That's not like you.
Now I'm screwed...
If it's okay with you, I was thinking
about taking on this case...
How about it?
Great...
But don't do anything that will
leave a scar on your career.
I'm going to take full
responsibility if you should fail.
So?
Check up on out those around the
Minister for anything unusual and
find out exactly what was going
on inside the restaurant...
I will look into the relationship between
the army and the Ichinose Report.
Oh? Isn't he your friend?
Of course, that's why I'm the
one who's investigating it!
Erasing his own memory... He sure has guts...
There might have been side-effects on his brain...
And I'm being laughed at by everyone...
A waste of money, isn't it?
If you're going to bother with shooting practice...
I recommend that you get an artificial body...
Are you saying I should become a cyborg?
I'm not stupid enough to mix orders
for work-related and private matters.
I think your shooting back
there was pretty good, but
If you thought Ur armour piercing bullets
were going to hit the hostages,
you should have dealt with it
according to the situation.
You did have your 9mm pistol with you, right?
Why do you think I pulled
you out of central office?
Don't you think it's better to try and contribute by
doing what you're good at instead of being depressed?
We're going to closely examine what was going
on for the ten-odd minutes before our strike!
How's your grandson?
What do you think?
Boy you're impatient...
The Ichinose Report won't affect
the army in any financial way...
There's nothing you would be interested in either.
Government or Administration, who's idea was it?
Soldiers who would lose out because of it
aren't in a position to know about it...
"Don't search for what you don't
know, it's safer..." your words...
You haven't changed...
There's a new restaurant with good shrimp...
How about it?
Maybe next time...
The major is waiting.
What did you find out?
The picture of the "Willow"
room right after the incident,
and the video from the camera
inside the restaurant both bug me.
This man was supposed to have a spinal unit made
for him by the North American Neutron Company...
But, when we put all the parts together,
it turned out they couldn't be reassembled into the original one.
The next image is the foreign minister
and a geisha in front of the restroom.
With a geisha?
Yes, it seems that he was drunk and having
fun switching bodies with a geisha.
That's the visitor from the
North American Industry.
Does he "play" too?
I have no idea.
I didn't find any images of what
was going on inside the restroom.
Here comes his secretary, all
worried about the minister.
That's where the secretary was attacked...
This is different than what
the other visitor told us,
He said the visitor was
attacked before the secretary.
The chairman was pretty drunk,
but he told us he thought he heard
the secretary's scream first.
What did the secretary see...?
What did she see...?
Minister, can you walk?
Yeah, thanks for saving me.
Major! You said the minister liked to
switch bodies with geishas, right?
Yeah, so?
What if the minister had his brain core switched?
If they wanted the Ichinose Report,
They would need the minister's body, his looks...
The secretary must have witnessed the
minister's brain being switched...
Ishikawa!
Kubota! This is Aramaki!
About the Minister of Foreign Affairs...
The minister was here with the visitors from the
North American Industry Support Association...
They took the Ichinose Report with them!
They have the encoded version, so that
might buy us a little time, but...
Where is the minister now?
He's on his way to the airport.
He's going to give a speech at the party for the
North American Industry Support Association.
I heard he's flying to America.
Batou! Equip with L-2 it's an emergency!
After picking up Togusa and Saitou,
we'll head to the airport!
Minister!
We're very sorry, your private plane has been
delayed 15 minutes late due to bad weather...
Is that so...
We're moving out!
Minister!
Sorry for the delay, your jet is ready...
Please, hold it right there Minister!
Oh, it's you! Thank you for the other day...
Is something wrong?
I was sent here to give you this.
What is this?
To recuperate from illness, I
will resign from office...
Me? What's this about appointing my successor?
Now that you have read that document,
you are no longer a minister.
What!?
What authority do you have!?
From the Prime Minister, along with the
Government party, this is an official matter.
If you want to, go ahead and confirm it yourself.
Assemblyman, you are suspected of spying,
and of attempting political asylum
in a foreign country.
Please come with us to the station...
You!
Who do you think you are?
Stop!
He is not the minister you should be guarding!
We have the brain core secured...
You have a lot of explaining
to do about who you are...
Take him away...
She's going to have an operation, to have her brain
supported by Cyberbrain technology and micro-machines...
There's going to be some impairment in her speech centre,
but nothing that would be a difficulty in everyday life.
That's good.
This case... it's a shame we couldn't
solve it, but thanks for everything
Right after the incident, if you didn’t hold out, the police would
have gone in, shot the robots, and thought matters were settled...
Section 9 wouldn't have been involved, and by now, the media would be
in panic about the Minister of Foreign Affairs spying and in exile...
I still can't believe you got the papers needed
to persuade a politician in such a short time...
It's like they say, always be prepared...
There was no bad weather,
and the plane came late...
That is Public Safety Section 9...